<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SquareLemon Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SquareLemon Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 10:54:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>So you got hacked, what now?</title>
      <link>/2019/06/so-you-got-hacked-what-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 10:54:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/06/so-you-got-hacked-what-now/</guid>
      <description>If you have just found out that one of your accounts has been hacked, you probably have a lot of questions. One of which is how to you undo whatever has been done and regain control. This is a good first question and I will attempt to cover this and the accompanying &amp;ldquo;how did this happen?&amp;rdquo;. The why and the who part can be more nuanced and very contextual so I&amp;rsquo;m going to steer away from that for now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Signal, Use Tor</title>
      <link>/2016/11/use-signal-use-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 23:49:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/use-signal-use-tor/</guid>
      <description>At times when people are likely to be out protesting or performing acts of civil disobedience all the advice comes out about how to conduct good OPSEC. Some advice is good, some is bad, some is well intentioned, and some it just dangerous.
We often hear &amp;quot;Use signal, use tor&amp;quot; mentioned. It has become a mantra uttered both ironically and unironically as the goto advice from a number of people. But this lacks context, nuance, and a key bit of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SecTor 2016 Presentation</title>
      <link>/2016/10/sector-2016-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/sector-2016-presentation/</guid>
      <description>A week ago I gave my talk &amp;ldquo;[Ab]Using TLS for Defensive Wins&amp;rdquo; at SecTor 2016. Here is my little blurb:
 TLS, and it’s older forerunner SSL, are used to maintain the confidentiality and integrity of network communications. This is a double edged sword for Information Security departments as this allows private information to remain private, but can also be used to hide malicious activity.
Current defensive measures for dealing with network traffic encrypted using TLS typically takes one of two forms; attempting to detect malicious activities via other means which are outside of the encrypted session, such as endpoint security tools and IP address blacklists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FingerPrinTLS Example Use Cases</title>
      <link>/2016/08/fingerprintls-example-use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 12:14:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/08/fingerprintls-example-use-cases/</guid>
      <description>I have unbroken my blog, so in preparation for BlackHat Arsenal I have written up a few use cases for FingerPrinTLS. The specific examples I have given are:
 Supplementing IDS Malware hunting and enhancing ThreatIntel(sorry!) Feeds Protecting API endpoints and Web Servers Canaries for Unicorns  Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FingerPrintTLS</title>
      <link>/fingerprintls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 11:17:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fingerprintls/</guid>
      <description>Introduction FingerprinTLS is a tool used to perform TLS Fingerprinting either via realtime sniffing of an network interface or via reading a PCAP file from the filesystem.
At the time of writing the main features are:
 Detection of:  TLS connection irrespective of port numbers or IP addresses Detection within IPv4, IPv6, 6in4, 6rd, and Teredo packets. Detection within 802.1Q packets.  Logging of events to JSON format log Automatic fingerprinting of unknown connections Export of unknown fingerprints (JSON format) Save client hello packets of unrecognized connections to a separate PCAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things are coming...</title>
      <link>/2016/01/things-are-coming.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/01/things-are-coming.../</guid>
      <description>I realise that I have not posted for a while, so I just wanted to drop a quick mini-post&amp;rsquo;ette to say that I have been working hard on a number of things to do with my TLS Fingerprinting side project. If you keep track of my GitHub page you&amp;rsquo;ll probably see the fruits of my labour first.
I&amp;rsquo;m planning on creating a number of posts on using the FingerPrinTLS tool once I have a few more key items in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TLS fingerprinting</title>
      <link>/tls-fingerprinting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tls-fingerprinting/</guid>
      <description>Background Transport Layer Security (TLS) provides security in the form of encryption to all manner of network connections from legitimate financial transactions, to private conversations, and malware calling home. The inability for an eavesdropper to analyze this encrypted traffic protects its users, whether they are legitimate or malicious. Those using TLS operate under the assumption that although an eavesdropper can easily observe the existence of their session, its source and destination IP addresses, that the content itself is secure and unreadable without access to cryptographic keying material at one or both ends of the connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tls fingerprinting resources</title>
      <link>/2015/09/tls-fingerprinting-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/tls-fingerprinting-resources/</guid>
      <description>Today I gave my talk at DerbyCon, &amp;ldquo;Stealthier Attacks &amp;amp; Smarter Defending with TLS Fingerprinting&amp;rdquo;. The links to all the resources are:
 Paper / Post giving a technical overview of the fingerprinting technique discussed. Slides from the talk, which probably don&amp;rsquo;t make much sense without the talk. Tools discussed during the talk  Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to join in the conversation on twitter too either to my account or the FingerprinTLS account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, I&#39;ve been quiet</title>
      <link>/2015/09/yes-ive-been-quiet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/yes-ive-been-quiet/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted for a while, largely because I have been working on some research that I have been doing, and am presenting at both SecTor in a few weeks, and DerbyCon tomorrow. I will be releasing some materials relating to this talk so that people who are not in attendance can obtain the information without having to listen to me on a recording, so if you are interested in TLS Fingerprinting, keep an eye out tomorrow as I will be publishing a longer than normal post with some of the technical details and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mitm the mitmers</title>
      <link>/2015/06/mitm-the-mitmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/mitm-the-mitmers/</guid>
      <description>Last week I mentioned that James Arlen and I gave the closing keynote at SCCongress Toronto. We had planned to do a live demo as part of the talk, but after reaching the venue and connecting to the wifi we found that it would not work as planned, specifically because the venue wifi was &amp;ldquo;correcting&amp;rdquo; my tampering of the DNS on the demo victim, they were still visiting the real website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sc congress toronto</title>
      <link>/2015/06/sc-congress-toronto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/06/sc-congress-toronto/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday James Arlen and I gave the closing Keynote at SC Congress Toronto.
If you would like to see the slides, we have made the available on slideshare:
 And the pre-recorded demo is available here (the live demo was, unfortunately, not recorded):
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bsides toronto 2015 is coming...</title>
      <link>/2015/05/bsides-toronto-2015-is-coming.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/bsides-toronto-2015-is-coming.../</guid>
      <description>Returning for it&amp;rsquo;s third year, BSides Toronto has just been announced for 7th November 2015 and the CFP opened, so if you want to speak get your submission in! (details on the BSidesTO website).
Keep an eye out on Twitter too as announcements when registration opens, speakers are announced, etc.
I won&amp;rsquo;t be speaking this year because I have the pleasure of taking one of the spots as an organiser for the conference, so I will definitely be there&amp;hellip; lurking :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stealthier attacks and smarter defending with tls fingerprinting</title>
      <link>/2015/05/stealthier-attacks-and-smarter-defending-with-tls-fingerprinting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/stealthier-attacks-and-smarter-defending-with-tls-fingerprinting/</guid>
      <description>I am really pleased to announce that I have decided to try my hand at talking at conferences again this year and have a new talk ready &amp;ldquo;Stealthier Attacks and Smarter Defending with TLS Fingerprinting&amp;rdquo;. Despite being a talk on TLS (and SSL) there isn&amp;rsquo;t any complex crypto or mathematics, this is aimed at defenders and attackers rather than cryptographers. Here&amp;rsquo;s the abstract:
 Ever been busted because you man in the middle software (which does TLS properly) alerted someone to your bad certificate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mitm in telecoms networks i told you so ... sort of</title>
      <link>/2015/03/mitm-in-telecoms-networks-i-told-you-so-...-sort-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/mitm-in-telecoms-networks-i-told-you-so-...-sort-of/</guid>
      <description>For anyone that has read this blog before, you will probably know that at the end of 2014 I gave my &amp;ldquo;Corporation in The Middle&amp;rdquo; talk at both SecTor and BSides Toronto. In short my ISP (Rogers) used a platform to Man (Corporation) in The Middle my and every other customers connection in order to insert notification banners at the top of pages in certain circumstances, such approaching your bandwidth cap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quick and dirty crapware analysis ids rule creation foo</title>
      <link>/2015/03/quick-and-dirty-crapware-analysis-ids-rule-creation-foo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/quick-and-dirty-crapware-analysis-ids-rule-creation-foo/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have made some brief posts on the Snort/Suricata rules that I wrote to detect SuperFish and PrivDog, two pieces of Crapware/Malware/Adware/PUP that insert themselves as a Certificate Authority in the local browsers and proceed to Man in the Middle HTTPS traffic for the purposes of injecting ads.
In those posts I mentioned that CipherSuite fingerprinting was the key to creating the rules, however I didn&amp;rsquo;t give a very comprehensive technical blow-by-blow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>privdog detection</title>
      <link>/2015/02/privdog-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/privdog-detection/</guid>
      <description>In much the same way as I was able to detect hosts infected with SuperFish by profiling the changes in Cipher Suites used in their SSL connections (by virtue of SuperFish essentially having it&amp;rsquo;s own SSL client) I have been able to create a fingerprint for PrivDog. For those who are interested, the ciphersuites used by the PrivDog client are: Cipher Suites (44 suites) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc014) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_ECDSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc00a) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_DSS_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc022) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc021) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0x0039) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0x0038) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc00f) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_ECDSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0xc005) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_AES_256_CBC_SHA (0x0035) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc013) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_ECDSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc009) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_DSS_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc01f) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc01e) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0x0033) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0x0032) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc00e) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_ECDSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0xc004) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_AES_128_CBC_SHA (0x002f) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_SHA (0xc011) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_ECDSA_WITH_RC4_128_SHA (0xc007) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_SHA (0xc00c) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_ECDSA_WITH_RC4_128_SHA (0xc002) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_SHA (0x0005) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_MD5 (0x0004) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_SEED_CBC_SHA (0x009a) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_WITH_SEED_CBC_SHA (0x0099) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_SEED_CBC_SHA (0x0096) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_DES_CBC_SHA (0x0015) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_WITH_DES_CBC_SHA (0x0012) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_DES_CBC_SHA (0x0009) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_EXPORT_WITH_DES40_CBC_SHA (0x0014) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_EXPORT_WITH_DES40_CBC_SHA (0x0011) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_EXPORT_WITH_DES40_CBC_SHA (0x0008) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_RSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc012) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDHE_ECDSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc008) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_DSS_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc01c) Cipher Suite: TLS_SRP_SHA_RSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc01b) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_RSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0x0016) Cipher Suite: TLS_DHE_DSS_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0x0013) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_RSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc00d) Cipher Suite: TLS_ECDH_ECDSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0xc003) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA (0x000a) Cipher Suite: TLS_RSA_WITH_IDEA_CBC_SHA (0x0007) Cipher Suite: TLS_EMPTY_RENEGOTIATION_INFO_SCSV (0x00ff)  I have updated my Interception Snort Rules to include this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>superfish detection</title>
      <link>/2015/02/superfish-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/superfish-detection/</guid>
      <description>Much has been in the press the past couple of days regarding Superfish, specifically being pre-installed on Lenovo hardware, however the issues discussed are relevant to any device with Superfish installed. It just so happens that Lenovo made the decision to bundle it up in the factory.
There are a number of write-ups on the technical nature of this malware/adware, and I won&amp;rsquo;t attempt to rehash those, they are most likely better than anything that I could contribute anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>man in the middle reach grows</title>
      <link>/2015/02/man-in-the-middle-reach-grows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/man-in-the-middle-reach-grows/</guid>
      <description>With all the talk of Lenovo and Superfish in the press, now seems a good time to mention an update which is personal to me on the topic of Man in The Middle attacks.
People have asked me how widespread the man in the middle attempts made my by ISP actually are. Well thankfully the manufacturer of the equipment used has put out a press statement around their current &amp;ldquo;subscriber reach&amp;rdquo; which you can read in full here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the value of cloud security report</title>
      <link>/2015/02/the-value-of-cloud-security-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/the-value-of-cloud-security-report/</guid>
      <description>Today my employer, Leviathan Security, released three reports written by James Arlen, Brendan O&amp;rsquo;Connor and myself on the overarching topic of Cloud Security.
I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to say that they seem to have been well received by the press. ZDNet (twice), IT World Canada &amp;amp; CloudWedge have all picked up on it so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>os x sandbox quickstart</title>
      <link>/2015/02/os-x-sandbox-quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/os-x-sandbox-quickstart/</guid>
      <description>The sandbox feature on OS X is really useful for restricting what applications have access to in more granular and controlled fashion than standard file permissions allow. However writing the initial sandbox profile can be problematic for many users, it&amp;rsquo;s not always clear what an application needs access to in order to operate in the expected way; there are a number of system files, libraries and such like, that an application quite rightly needs to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brakeing down security podcast isp man in the middle</title>
      <link>/2015/02/brakeing-down-security-podcast-isp-man-in-the-middle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/brakeing-down-security-podcast-isp-man-in-the-middle/</guid>
      <description>I made a return visit to the Brakeing Down Security as a guest to discuss ISPs who Man in The Middle their customers. We discuss my Corporation in The Middle talk from SecTor &amp;amp; BSidesTO. Thanks again to Bryan and Brian for having me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brakeing down security podcast threat modeling</title>
      <link>/2015/02/brakeing-down-security-podcast-threat-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/brakeing-down-security-podcast-threat-modeling/</guid>
      <description>This week I was lucky enough to be a guest on the Brakeing Down Security podcast, the specific episode is available here, or you can subscribe to the podcast here. Thanks to Bryan and Brian for having me :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>citm snort rules</title>
      <link>/2015/01/citm-snort-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/citm-snort-rules/</guid>
      <description>Last year I gave my Corporation In The Middle talk in which I explained how my ISP has been man-in-the-middle&amp;rsquo;ing my connection to inject a warning banner into the top of webpages I visited (talk content here and here).
Part of this involved traffic analysis to discover artifacts of the injection process. In an effort to make this process more automated, repeatable and accessible I have put together a few snort rules to allow others to alert on this condition:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mitm at 30,000 feet</title>
      <link>/2015/01/mitm-at-30000-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/mitm-at-30000-feet/</guid>
      <description>In the past week I have seen a few mentions on twitter regarding Gogo Air presenting fake SSL certs for YouTube to users of their in air Internet access service:
hey @Gogo, why are you issuing *.google.com certificates on your planes? pic.twitter.com/UmpIQ2pDaU
&amp;mdash; Adrienne Porter Felt (@apf) January 2, 2015 

No, not OK. @Gogo please justify breaking the Internet for your paying users. Huge privacy connotations! pic.twitter.com/AxZOPEK0oO
&amp;mdash; Ben Hughes (@benjammingh) January 4, 2015</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no we dont</title>
      <link>/2015/01/no-we-dont/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/no-we-dont/</guid>
      <description>I just got a festive present from my ISP, Rogers.
Following my recent talks regarding ISP packet injection/interception and data collection I wrote to the privacy officer at Rogers and asked, under PIPEDA, that I be supplied all information regarding my account, including any information that they have gathered such as URLs of sites visited, etc.
I got a fairly standard response which said that they did not collect any such data, to which I replied: Hi,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bsides toronto video and slides</title>
      <link>/2014/12/bsides-toronto-video-and-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/12/bsides-toronto-video-and-slides/</guid>
      <description>At the end of November I gave my talk, &amp;ldquo;Corporation In The Middle [BSidesTO Edition]&amp;rdquo; at BSides Toronto 2014. The recording of the talk is now online and available here:
 You can play along at home with the slides, here:
  Corporation In The Middle - BSidesTO Edition  from Lee Brotherston  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>corporation in the middle blog edition</title>
      <link>/2014/11/corporation-in-the-middle-blog-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/11/corporation-in-the-middle-blog-edition/</guid>
      <description>I recently gave a talk entitled Corporation In The Middle. This post is a summary for the benefit of people who don&amp;rsquo;t want to listen to the recording or try to make sense of my slides without the commentary.
Background Towards the end of 2013 I noticed that my ISP was inserting banners into webpages to notify me when I consumed 75% or more of my monthly bandwidth allowance. Nothing suspicious you may think, it is after all a perfectly reasonable message to relay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>corporation in the middle</title>
      <link>/2014/10/corporation-in-the-middle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/10/corporation-in-the-middle/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I presented my talk, &amp;ldquo;Corporation In The Middle&amp;rdquo; at SecTor 2014. I will be presenting an updated and truncated version of the talk at BSides Toronto in November of this year.
If you are interested in seeing the talk you can do so here:  If so inclined, you can also get the slides here. The original blurb was: My ISP deliberately MiTM&amp;rsquo;d my connection. This talk discusses how they did it, how I detected what they did and what this means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>is your eula lowering your application security</title>
      <link>/2014/07/is-your-eula-lowering-your-application-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/07/is-your-eula-lowering-your-application-security/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I tweeted this:
 I&amp;#39;m pretty sure when your EULA prohibits reverse engineering your software, all you prevent is people telling you that they reversed it.
&amp;mdash; leE Brotherston (@leEb_public) July 15, 2014  
Quite a lot of people agreed (at the time of writing it has 40 retweets and 19 favourites, which is quite a lot for me), so I thought that I would expand and explain this in a little more detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sector 2014</title>
      <link>/2014/05/sector-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/05/sector-2014/</guid>
      <description>I was meant to start this blog with a post about my ISP, about how they had man in the middle&amp;rsquo;d my connection and how I had been working out the details of why they had been doing this, how they achieved it and how I uncovered what they had been up to.
Since I started writing that post the topic has grown somewhat and now I have been confirmed as a speaker at SecTor 2014 in Toronto.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>